-准备好了吗  -好了
- Ready? - Yeah.
-你好  这是  -瑞秋
- Hi, it's  - Rachel
-和  -菲比的家
- and  - Phoebe's.
-请  -在哔声后...
- Please... -leave--
在哔声后...
Leave.
那个我说过了
But l just said "leave."
我知道  因为你都分到好词
l know because you have all the good words.
而我呢  只分到"这是"  "和"
What do l get? l get "it's," "and."
还有"留言"  我不要
Oh, l'm sorry, l have "a." Forget it.
菲比  拜托  别闹了
Phoebe, come on, that's silly.
好  那我们交换
All right. So let's switch.
不要  我都分到好词
No, l have all the good words.
好吧  好吧  我们来交换
Okay, fine, fine. We can switch.
-好  -好
- Okay. - Okay.
-嗨...  -大家好
-  Hi... - ...everybody...
-这是...  -瑞秋...
- ...it's... - ...Rachel...
-和...  -菲比的家
- ...and... - ...Phoebe's.
请...慢着
Please...Wait.
-你怎么办到的  -什么
- How did you do that? - What?
我懂了  你是个腹黑的室友
Oh, you're no ordinary roommate, are you?
菲比  待会再录好吗
Phoebe, come on can we finish this later?
我想在天黑前去慢跑
Cause l'm going running before it gets dark.
-你也一起来嘛  -真的吗
- Oh! Why don't you come with me? - Really?
对  一定很好玩  我们去公园跑步
Yeah, lt'll be fun! We'll run in the park.
当做室友间第一次联络感情
It'll be like our first you know, roommate bonding thing.
好  我们去跑步
Okay, let's go running!
而且那里有帅哥哦
Yeah, and there's  really cute guys there.
-那就往他们跑过去  -没问题
- Let's run towards them! - Okay.
你等我一下
Wait just one more second.
嗨  这是瑞秋和菲比的家
Hi, it's Phoebe and Rachel's.
请在哔声后留言  谢谢
Please leave a message. Thanks!
等等  你都讲完了
No, Wait a minute. You took all the words!
你遇到对手了  瑞秋·格林
You've met your match, Rachel Greene!
我刚看完一本很棒的书
So l just finished this fascinating book.
到了2030年  会出现
By the year 2030, there'll be computers...
跟人脑一样功能复杂的电脑
...that can carry out the same amount of functions as an actual human brain.
所以理论上你可以把思想和记忆
So, theoretically, you could download...your thoughts
下载到这种电脑上
and memories into this computer...
然后以机器的形态长生不死
...and live forever as a machine.
我刚发现我能睁着眼睛睡觉
And l just realized l can sleep with my eyes open.
把箱子钉在地上真是聪明
Honey, it was a great idea, nailing the boxes to the floor.
我没把箱子钉在地上啊
l didn't nail the boxes to the floor.
所以他们是可以搬开吗
So you can move them!
可以  我这就搬
Yes, and while l'm doing that,
罗斯有个很好听的电脑故事哦
Ross has a great computer story for you.
大家好
Hey, everybody!
这是吉宁
l'd like you to meet Janine.
她是我的新室友
She's gonna be my new roommate!
你好  她要来跟我住
And she's gonna live with me!
很高兴认识你  吉宁...
lt's nice to meet you. Janine...?
勒夸  吉宁·勒夸
Le Croix.  Janine Le Croix.
我都不知道  好好听的姓
l didn't know that. What a pretty last name.
你是哪里人
So where are you from?
澳洲人  我几周前刚搬过来
Australia. I just moved here a couple of weeks ago
-来自地球的另一边吗  -对
- From the land down under? - Yeah.
这个我也不知道
l didn't know that either!
你做哪一行
So what do you do?
-我是个舞者  -你是个舞者
- l'm a dancer. - You're a dancer?
她是个舞者
She's a dancer!
-我要去整理东西了  -我帮你开门
- l think l'll go unpack. - Let me, let me.
-乔伊  -有何贵干
- Joey. - Yeah?
你叫这个女人搬来之前  有先面试吗
Did you interview this woman before you asked her to move in?
当然有
Of course I did!
你到底问了什么
what exactly did you ask her?
"你什么时候可以搬来"
When can you move in?
谢谢你把她带到我们身边
Thank you for bringing her into our lives.
我的老天啊
Unbelievable.
这堆箱子好占地方啊
Look at all the boxes!
我迫不及待要约她出去了
l cannot wait to ask her out.
等等  乔伊
Wait a minute. Joey!
你不能约她  她是你的室友
Joey, You can't. She's your roommate.
那样事情会变复杂
It-it'll be way too complicated.
没错  千万不要
Yeah, yeah, man don't do it.
你约了她  我就不能约她了
l mean, if you date her, then l can't date her.
还记得你跟那唐娜交往  分手后
Remember when you were going out with that girl Donna and you guys broke up
你们之后在超市偶遇的尴尬事
Remember how horrible it was when you guys bumped into each other
-你没忘吧  -哎哟妈呀
- at the supermarket? - Oh, God, yeah.
想像你就住在超市里
Now imagine you live at the supermarket.
好啊
Okay!
-不是  不是  -你说得对
- No-no! - You're right!
我不想那样  我不能约她
l don't want that. l can't date her.
最好也别跟她调情
You'd better watch the flirting too,
因为你们住得这么近  可能会出事
Cause you know, in such close quarters, it could be trouble.
太难了  莫妮卡
Well, that's gonna be tough, Mon. I mean,
毕竟美女当前  我很难不去...
lt's hard for me to be around an attractive woman
跟她调情
and...and not flirt.
我老是在你面前  你也没怎样啊
You're around me all the time, and you don't flirt.
有点难过是吧  小甜心
A little sad about that, sweetie?
我要绑鞋带  你先跑  我就来  好
l have to tie my shoes, so you go ahead. l'll catch up.
-好的  -好
- Okay. - Okay.
拜托  那哪叫跑步  快点
Come on, that's not running! Let's go!
我是说真的  她跑步的时候
You guys, l'm telling you, when she runs...
就像芝麻街里的大青蛙
...she looks like a cross between Kermit The Frog
和生化机器人合体
...and the Six Million Dollar Man.
莫妮卡以前好喜欢他
Monica had such a crush on him.
她睡觉之前都会亲他的海报
She used to kiss his poster every night before she went to bed.
我也会
l used to do that too!
那你有大青蛙的专辑  "全身绿色的烦恼"吗
Did you also have his album, "lt's Not Easy Being Green"?
莫妮卡...
Oh, Mon.
所以菲比的姿势很怪
So Phoebe runs weird, huh?
对  而且她还会想再去跑步
Yeah, yeah and you know what, I know she's gonna wanna run again,
我不知道怎么躲掉
l don't know how to get out of it.
毕竟我跟她住在一起
l mean, l live with her.
干脆你直接一点  实话实说嘛
Why don't you be straight with her? Tell her the truth.
你说得对
You're right.
你说得对  我应该跟她直说
You're right. l should just tell her the truth.
菲比  莫妮卡把我绊倒
Pheebs, Monica tripped me.
我这辈子再也不能跑步了
l don't think l can ever run again, ever!
你为什么要绊倒她
Why? Why would you do that?
我不知道
l don't know.
瑞秋  抱歉害你两个脚踝受伤
Rachel, l'm sorry l hurt your ankles.
-只伤了一个  -等着瞧
- Ankle. - We'll see.
好  东西都拿出来了
Okay. l am officially unpacked.
多谢帮忙
Thanks for helping me, man.
乔伊
Joe?
看来他回家了
Well, l guess Joey went home.
看  还有一个箱子没拆
And look, there is still one box l have to unpack.
你被骗了
l got you!
天哪  我差点被吓出心脏病
Oh, my God, you almost gave me a heart attack.
我憋笑憋得好辛苦
lt was so hard not to laugh.
收拾的挺不错啊
Hey, the place looks great.
是啊  还不赖吧  莫妮卡今天要加班
Yeah, Not bad, right? You know what? Monica's working late,
我要把这里打扫得一尘不染
so l'm gonna make this place spotless.
你知道我还要干嘛吗
You know what else I'm gonna do, know what else I'm gonna do?
我还要下楼去买花送她
l'm gonna go downstairs and get her some flowers.
谁会不想跟我住
Who wouldn't want to live with me?
我不想
l don't.
我想跟性感澳洲舞者住
No, l want to live with the super- hot Australian dancer!
情况如何了
How's that going, though?
你忍得住不打情骂俏吗
Are you okay with the not-flirting thing?
目前还可以  但是好辛苦哦
Yeah. Well, so far yeah. But it's tough.
我的调情能量一直在累积
l've got this built-up flirting energy,
而且无处发泄
and l don't know how to get rid of it.
你好吗  美人
How you doing?
天啊
Oh, man!
抱歉  客厅比较宽
Sorry. There's just more room out here.
没事没事  我只是
No-no-no-no-no,  you just uh,
想到我也该拉拉筋了
reminded me that l have to do my stretches too.
你应该更...
Why don't you try to be...?
-怎么了  -没事
- What's wrong? - Nothing.
我只不想让你碰到我
l didn't want you to touch me...
因为我拉筋拉得全身是汗
...because l'm all sweaty from the workout.
我去洗个澡
l'm gonna hit the shower.
我的天
Oh, my God!
抱歉在浴室晾衣服
Sorry about that stuff hanging in there.
我的丁字裤很娇贵  不能用烘干机
lt's just my thongs are too delicate for the dryer.
没错  是我
Oh, yeah, it's me.
我看到你早上拿慢跑鞋  然后溜出来
l saw you grab your running shoes this morning and sneak out.
你骗我好独自跑步
You lied so you could run by yourself.
不是的  菲比  我是...
No, Phoebe, no. l was....
我只是跑跑看...
l was actually just checking...
看我
...to see...
能不能跑  结果可以
...if l could run. And l can!
拜托  瑞秋  我又不是白痴
Please, Rachel, l'm not an idiot.
等等  菲比
No, wait. Phoebe?
真是夫妻住久了  举止会越来越像啊
Couples who live together do start to look alike.
莫德勒...
So, Mondler....
你这是在干嘛
What are you doing?
你说呢  我在打扫啊
What does it look like? l am cleaning.
你动她的东西  有经过她同意吗
Did you get Monica's authorization to move all her stuff?
没必要  我会把东西都放回去
Authorization? I don't need that. l'll put everything back.
完全恢复原状吗
Put it back exactly where you found it?
当然是完全恢复原状
Yes. l'm gonna put it back exactly where l found it.
首先  这种态度对你没有帮助
First of all, that attitude is not helping.
她才不会在乎有没有恢复原状
She won't care if l put her stuff back in the same stupid place.
你是刚认识莫妮卡吗
Hello? Did you just meet Monica?
她会觉得我做得很好
She'll recognize that l did a nice thing...
并感到窝心
...and appreciate it.
其实这样也蛮好的
Actually, this will work out well.
等你必须搬回去跟乔伊住
Because when you have to move back with Joey...
乔伊的新室友就可以来跟我住
...Joey's hot new roommate can come live with me.
我懂了
Oh, l see, I see.
你想吓唬我
You're trying to freak me out.
钱德勒  莫妮卡
Look, Chandler, Monica is really weird
对这种事有怪癖
about this kind of stuff, all right?
相信我  我跟她住了十六年
Believe me, l lived with her for 1 6 years.
她一定会抓狂
She's going to freak out.
我的天  她会坐扁你
Oh, my God. She's going to sit on you.
她才不会  我证明给你看
No, she is not. Okay? You know l'll prove it to you.
我现在就打给她
l'll call her right now.
电话擦好了
Phone's done.
-莫妮卡  工作如何  -烂透了
- Hey, Mon. How's it going? - Terrible.
如果我要把事情搞好的话
If-if I want something done right,
那就全要亲力亲为
l have to do it myself.
其他人只会搞砸
Other people just wreck stuff.
我真觉得我今晚可能会杀人
l really think l might kill someone tonight.
别这样  没那么糟吧
Come on, come on, it can't be that bad.
是非常糟
It's worse.
想到快见到你了
The only thing getting me through...
我才撑得下去
...is knowing l'll see you soon.
我搞不好会设法早退  不要...
l might even try to get out of here early.
不要  不要  不要
No! No-no-no-no-no-no.
不要了吧  餐厅似乎很需要你
No, no. It sounds like they need you there.
-你跟罗斯在一起吗  -一切都很好  再见
- You're just hanging out with Ross? - lt's all good! Okay, bye!
她会宰了我
She's gonna kill me.
电话放反了
The phone was facing the other way.
相框应该摆在上面
And that goes back up there.
你知道我们要怎么做吗
You know what we should do ?
先从大型家具复原起  那比较简单
We should start with the big stuff, you know? That'll be the easiest.
先搬沙发
So let's start with the couch.
我没问题
l got it.
位置好像不对
That doesn't look right.
什么意思
What are you talking about?
沙发刚好跟毯子对齐
The couch is perfectly in line with the carpet.
我可以走到这边  轻松的把脚翘在...
Then l can just walk over here and casually put my feet up on....
好  好  我们这样吧
Okay, okay, here's what we do.
把沙发往茶几那边推
We move the couch closer to the coffee table.
那沙发的背后  就不会跟毯子边缘对齐了
But then the back of the couch won't line up with the back of the carpet.
那我们就把茶几往沙发
OK, well, here.We'll just move the coffee table...
那边推
...closer to the couch.
那茶几就不在座位区正中央了
But then the coffee table won't be centered in the seating area.
那茶几就和桌子就不搭配了
But the coffee table doesn't match the table!
罗斯
Ross!
我该怎么办
Look, what am l gonna do?
我不调情  却还是
l'm not flirting, but still...
强烈被她吸引  就像飞蛾被火吸引
l'm drawing her to me like a moth to a flame!
这里是怎么了
What the hell's going on over here?
莫妮卡会宰了你
Monica's gonna kill you!
我需要你们的帮忙
Look, I need your help. Okay?
我得想办法把这个女人吓跑
l have to do something to repel this woman.
等等  等等
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
你们最会把女人吓跑了
You guys repel women all the time!
我可是结过三次婚的人
Hey, l've been married three times.
不不不  我亲眼见识过
No, no, no. l've seen it happen.
你们跟女人交往得好好的
You get a rapport going with a woman,
最后却总是能搞砸
but somehow you manage to kill it.
你们的秘诀是什么
What's your secret?
我们并不会把女人吓跑
Look, we do not repel women, okay?
完全没有这回事
That is completely untrue.
我们确实会
Oh, yes, we do, my man.
记不记得大学时参加春季舞会
Remember when we were back in college and we went to that spring dance
你走到心仪的女生前
And you walked right up to that girl you liked
却大谈爱尔兰土豆饥荒
and you could not stop talking about the Irish potato famine?
那你呢  你当年也没那么受欢迎啊
What about you? You weren't you know, so hot in college either
他每次说完话都会这样
After everything he said, he'd go-
莫妮卡也不喜欢  也许我应该改掉
Yeah, Monica doesn't like that either. Maybe l should stop doing that.
对了  女生不喜欢跟我聊科学
Oh you know what, girls don't like it when I start talking about science.
是人都不喜欢
That's not specific to girls.
太好了  还有呢
This is great, this is great. What else? What else?
她们不喜欢你纠正她们的文法
Uh, they don't like it when you correct their grammar.
她们不喜欢你解释  你的笑话哪里好笑
And they don't like it when you explain why your jokes are funny.
她们不喜欢你一直问她们  喜不喜欢你
They don't like it when you keep asking them if they like you.
天啊  幸好我有莫妮卡
Man, l am so lucky l have Monica.
我永远也找不到真爱了
l'm never gonna find love again.
-菲比  可以跟你谈一谈吗  -可以
- Phoebe, Can l talk to you for a second? - Sure.
好的
Okay.
菲比  我只是想跟你道歉
Phoebe, look, l just wanted to say l'm sorry, okay?
这事情我处理得很差
l handled the situation horribly.
而且我不该骗你
And l should not have lied to you.
那你应该怎样
So what should you have done?
我应该跟你说实话
l should have told you the truth.
而实话是...
Which is?
我之所以不想跟你跑步
Well, you know the reason that l didn't want to go running with you is...
是因为...
...because...
你跑步的姿势有点...
...the way that you run is just a little....
-所以呢  -很尴尬
- So? - lt's embarrassing.
别人都当我们是疯子
People were looking at us like we were crazy.
-你干嘛在意  -因为他们是人
- Why do you care? - Because they're people!
是你不认识也不会再见到的人
People you don't know and will never see again.
但他们依旧是人
Yes, but still they are people...
还有眼睛呢
...with eyes.
我就不怕跟喘气小姐跑步啊
l didn't get embarrassed running next to Miss....
但是好吧
But no, okay
难怪你会觉得  跟我跑步很尴尬
No, no, l can see why running with me would be embarrassing to you.
你很极端保守的
Okay. You're uptight.
什么  我才不保守呢.
What? l am not uptight.
听着  我才不保守  老兄
Listen, l am not uptight, man.
没关系  我不是在批评你
That's okay. Rach. l'm not judging you.
你就是这样
That's just who you are.
我就比较自由
Me, l'm more free, you know.
我从小就这样跑
You know, l run like l did when l was a kid...
因为这样才好玩
...because that's the only way it's fun, you know?
你从来没有往前冲到  腿好像快断了吗
Didn't you ever run so fast you thought your legs would fall off...
例如要跑去玩荡秋千
...like when you were running towards the swings
或是在躲魔鬼时
or running away from Satan?
躲邻居的狗
The neighbor's dog.
这盏灯没摆错吧
Okay, is this in the right place?
管他的  我只会把女人吓跑
Who cares? l repel women.
不行不行  你不能进来
No, no, no! You can't come in here!
罗斯光着身体
Ross is naked!
-什么  -什么
- What?! - What?!
我不能说我光着身体
l couldn't say l was naked,
她可以看我光着身体
because she's allowed to see me naked.
为什么一定要有人光着身体呢
Why does anyone have to be naked?
罗斯为什么光着身体
Why is Ross naked?
我要给钱德勒看一个东西
l had to show Chandler something.
光着身体看
Naked?
对  我好像有
Yeah, I...I guess l have...
男人病
...a "guy" problem.
跟钱德勒的一样吗
ls it the same thing Chandler had?
听着  你就待会再回来
Look, just come back later.
等我们把一切搞定了  就可以进来了
We'll get everything squared away and you can come back later.
好  浴室洗手台底下
Okay, listen, there's still some of Chandler's medicine left
还有钱德勒的药
under the sink in the bathroom.
-再见  -再见
- Bye. - Bye!
谢天谢地
Thank God.
兄弟  你有什么病
Dude, what'd you have?
没时间了  我们必须专心
Look, we have no time, okay? We must focus.
我们得把一切恢复原状
We've got to get everything back into its original place.
相簿
The photo album!
相簿里有一大堆这公寓的照片
There were millions of pictures of the apartment in the photo album.
我们可以参考照片  把东西恢复原样
We just go through it and match everything to the pictures.
太好了  好主意
That's perfect! That's brilliant!
说真的  你有什么病
So, really, what'd you have?
乔伊  我帮你买了啤酒
Hey, Joe. l've got some beer for you.
是"帮尼"吧
Don't you mean "for whom"?
好
Sure.
我正想叫披萨
l was gonna order some pizza.
你要一起吃吗
You wanna share one?
披萨  我又不是没吃过
Pizza? lt's not like l never had that before.
有什么问题吗
ls something wrong?
好吧
All right, all right.
那我就直说了吧
Let's just get this out in the open, okay?
你很火辣
You're hot.
我很俊俏
l'm lovable.
我们两个显然很有感觉
Clearly, there's a vibe going on between us.
但我们是室友
But we're roommates...
这样下去会铸成大错的
...and it's a huge mistake for us to continue down this road.
-乔伊...  -不  我是说真的
- Joey... -  No, no, no, I'm telling ya.
想像你住在超市里
lmagine yourself living in a supermarket...
这样你就懂了吧
...and you'll understand.
所以我们该怎么办
Okay? So the question is, what do we do?
不怎么办
Well, I don't think there is anything to do.
我觉得你人很好
l think you're really sweet.
但是我对你没兴趣
But l'm not interested in you like that.
不是啦
No, l mean....
你人真的很好
You're a nice guy,
我很高兴能当你的室友和朋友
and l'm happy to be your roommate and your friend.
只是我对你
l'm just, you know, l just...
没有那种感觉
...don't feel that way about you.
我知道了
l see what happened.
因为我一直想把你吓跑
lt's because l was trying to repel you.
对吧  相信我
Right? Believe me,
等我一放电  情况就大不同
you'd feel a lot different if l turned it on.
-应该不会  -绝对会
- l don't think so. - Oh, l do.
你好吗  美人
How you doing?
我很好
l'm okay.
什么
What?
怎么了
我的天啊
Oh, dear God!
对不起  你说得对  感觉好爽
l'm so sorry. You're right. This feels great!
对吧  你不会在意别人的目光
See? And you don't care if people stare.
因为你很快就会跑没影了
lt's only a second. Cause then you're gone!
感觉真的好棒  我觉得好自由好优雅
lt's amazing! l feel so free and so graceful!
小心那匹马
Watch out for the horse.
我可以进去了吗
Is it okay for me to come in now?
-为什么东西都变了  -再见
- Why is everything different? - Bye.
没有变啊
l don't see anything different...
只不过你一进来
...other than the fact that the room got brighter
就让这个房间蓬荜生辉
when you came into it.
小茶几位置不对  沙发怪怪的
The end table is wrong, the couch looks bizarre...
更别提冰箱上的磁铁
...and don't even get me started on the refrigerator magnets.
好  你别生气  千万别生气
Okay look, don't...don't be mad okay?
我整理完东西  想做点让你高兴的事
But, after l unpacked the boxes, l wanted to do something nice for you...
所以我就大扫除
...so l cleaned the apartment.
我把东西乱搬  却忘了
So l moved everything around, and then l forgot...
该怎么恢复原状
...where it went back.
对不起  对不起  对不起
l'm sorry, l'm very sorry, l'm sorry.
没关系
That's okay.
钱德勒  你是在怕我吗
Chandler, Are you afraid of me or something?
你想我怕你吗
Do you want me to be afraid of you?
当然不要
Of course not.
拜托  钱德勒  你做了这么棒的事
My gosh, Chandler, what you did is a wonderful thing...
我真的很开心
...and l really appreciate it.
我知道我追求完美  所以有点强迫症
I know I have this weird thing where I want everything to be in the perfect place,
但我万万没想到你会担心这个
But l'd never expect you to worry about that.
真的
Really?
当然是真的
Of course.
你最好了
Oh, you're the best.
过来我抱抱
You come here to me.
等等  先做该做的事
Hold on, okay? First things first.
罗斯光着身体时坐过哪里
Did Ross sit anywhere while he was naked?
书上说到了2030年
So it said that by the year 2030,
会出现功能复杂的电脑
there'll be computers that can carry out the same number of functions
跟人脑一样
as an actual human brain.
所以理论上人可以把思想和记忆
So, theoretically, you could download your thoughts...
下载到这种电脑上
...and your memories into this computer- -
然后以机器的形态长生不死
And live forever as a machine.
吉尼  你知道我们现在在做什么吗
Janine, do you know what we're doing right now?
我们在资料传输
You and l, we're interfacing.
我该走了
Yeah, I gotta go.